Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Department of Theatre Records, 1911-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1911-2015, UWM Archival Collection 85; 14.3 cubic ft. (23 boxes)
  - 2. Production Files, 1911-2015, The production photographs consist of a mix of 8x10, 5x7, 4x6, and 3x5 sizes. Unless otherwise stated, all of the negatives are 35 mm safety film.
    - 2000-2015
      - Fan Yi Song, April 2001 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - The Kentucky Cycle, April 2001 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Phaedra, December 2001 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Everyman, February 2002 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Miss Julie Reconsidered, February 2002 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Fen, April 2002 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Welcome to the Moon, November 2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Milwaukee Shakespeare, November 2004 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Inspecting Carol, December 2004 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Milwaukee Stories: On (Not) Making It in America, December 2005 (Box 10, Folder 43)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Philadelphia Here I Come, March 2006 (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - From These Green Heights and A Raisin in the Sun, April 2006 (Box 10, Folder 40)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Einstein's Dreams, October 2006 (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: American Voices, November 2006 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - The Liar, December 2006 (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: Verseworks, February 2007 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Equus, March 2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Mr. Melancholy, March 2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - West Side Story, April 2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: Kenilworks, May 2007 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Shake Scenes, April 2008 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Showtune, February 2010 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - LabWorks: Starboard Home, February 2010 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - LabWorks: Unity (1918), April 2010 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Milkweed, September 2010 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - LabWorks: As It is in Heaven, October 2010 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - By the Bog of Cats, October 2010
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: Short Cuts, November 2010 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - The Love Talker, December 2010 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Hurry Up and Wait, December 2010 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Lover's Quarrel, December 2010
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: Finding Penelope, March 2011 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - The Last Days of Judas Iscariot, March 2011 (Box 10, Folder 45)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - The Second Best Bed: Shakespeare's Women Revealed, March 2011 (Box 10, Folder 45)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Aimee and Jaguar, April 2011
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Proof, April 2011
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - No, No, Nanette, May 2011 (Box 10, Folder 45)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: A Piece of my Heart, October 2011 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - The Sins of Sor Juana, October 2011 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - LabWorks: Stop/Kiss, December 2011 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - LabWorks: Into the Woods, March 2012
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - King Lear, November 2012 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - LabWorks: Uncommon Women and Others, December 2012 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Wild Party, February 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - LabWorks: Marisol, March 2013 (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Ruined, April 2013
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - LabWorks: Meet Me at the Avant Garde, May 2013 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - The Italian American Reconciliation, October 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Mil-Wonky Style and Mil-Wonky Too!, October 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - The Silk Hat Hot Spot, October 2013
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Les Liaisons Dangereuses, November 2013
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - It was Embarrassing, so Don't Ask, November 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Gint, December 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - LabWorks: Cementville, March 2014 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Laughing Stock, March 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Little Women the Musical, March 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Almost Maine, April 2014
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Cinderella, April 2014
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Urinetown the Musical, April 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Flourish Festival, May 2014 (Box 23)
      - Anton in Show Business, October 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Lysistrata, November 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Six Children's Plays for Adults, December 2014 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Love's Labour's Lost, April 2015 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - The Crucible, April 2015 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Unknown Productions, No. 1-8, undated
      - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 18-25)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Box 18, Folder 26)